Finding Aid for B. E. Muehlig’s Dry Goods Store (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records, 1900-1945
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
B. E. Muehlig’s Dry Goods Store (Ann Arbor, Mich.) records
1900-1945
B. E. Muehlig’s Dry Goods Store (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
8552 BB.2
39 oversize volumes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were received from Mrs. Fay Muehlig (donor no. 6725 ); other records were transferred from the Kempf House in Ann Arbor (donor no. 8483 ) in 2010.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
B. E. Muehlig's was an Ann Arbor, Michigan dry goods store.
The records of B. E. Muehlig's include cash books, ledgers, inventory record books, sales book, and bill register.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Commerce.; Variety stores--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Muehlig, Bertha E.
- Cash Books
  - Vol. no. 1, July 1912-February 1914 (Volume 1)
  - Vol. no. 2 (Volume 2)
    (volume not received)
  - Vol. no. 3, July 1915-October 1916 (Volume 3)
  - Vol. no. 4, October 1916-December 1917 (Volume 4)
  - Vol. no. 5, December 1917-January 1919 (Volume 5)
  - Vol. no. 6, January 1919-January 1920 (Volume 6)
  - Vol. no. 7, January 1920-November 1920 (Volume 7)
  - Vol. no. 8, November 1920-October 1921 (Volume 8)
  - Vol. nos. 10-12
    (volumes not received)
    - Vol. nos. 10-12 (Volume 10)
    - Vol. nos. 10-12 (Volume 11)
      (continued)
    - Vol. nos. 10-12 (Volume 12)
  - Vol. no. 13, December 1924-October 1925 (Volume 13)
  - Vol. no. 14 (Volume 14)
  - Vol. no. 15, July 1926-May 1927 (Volume 15)
  - Vol. no. 16, May 1927-February 1928 (Volume 16)
  - Vol. no. 17, February 1928-November 1928 (Volume 17)
  - Vol. no. 18, November 1928-August 1929 (Volume 18)
  - Vol. no. 19 (Volume 19)
    volume not received
  - Vol. no. 20, April 1930-January 1931 (Volume 20)
  - Vol. no. 21, January 1931-November 1931 (Volume 21)
  - Vol. no. 22, November 1931-February 1933 (Volume 22)
  - Vol. no. 23, February 1933-June 1934 (Volume 23)
  - Vol. no. 24 (Volume 24)
  - Vol. no. 25, August 1935-August 1936 (Volume 25)
  - Vol. no. 26, August 1936-September 1937 (Volume 26)
  - Vol. no. 27, September 1937-October 1938 (Volume 27)
  - Vol. no. 28, October 1938-October 1939 (Volume 28)
  - Vol. no. 29, October 1939-November 1940 (Volume 29)
  - Vol. no. 30, November 1940-October 1941 (Volume 30)
  - Vol. no. 31, October 1941-September 1942 (Volume 31)
  - Vol. no. 32, September 1942-August 1943 (Volume 32)
  - Vol. no. 33, August 1943-November 1944 (Volume 33)
  - Vol. no. 34, November 1944-June 1945 (Volume 34)
- Other Records
  - Ledgers
    - 1918
    - 1927
  - Journal, 1911-1932
  - February inventory record books, 1900-1939; 5 volumes
    - 1900-1911
    - 1912-1921
    - 1924-1927
    - 1933-1936
    - 1936-1939
  - Record book detailing daily sales, purchases, expenses, and bank account, 1916-1937
  - Sales Book
    - 1934-1938
  - Bill Register, undated; 2 volumes